{"data":[{"question":"She will be ready when he ________ here.","a":"get","b":"gets","c":"has got","d":"will get","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\/future tense + while\/when + simple present continuous\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The child always cries when his mother ________ out of the house.","a":"go","b":"goes","c":"will go","d":"has gone","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\/future tense + while\/when + simple present continuous\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"They often listen to the radio while they ________ in their car.","a":"is traveling","b":"travel","c":"will travel","d":"has traveled","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\/future tense + while\/when + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"We saw several old friends while we ________ in Baltimore.","a":"are","b":"were","c":"has been","d":"will be","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense\/past perfect tense + while\/when + simple past tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Raymond ________ two new shirts when he was downtown today.","a":"buy","b":"bought","c":"had bought","d":"has bought","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense\/past perfect tense + while\/when + simple past tense.\u00a0\n- This case \" simple pass tense \" is more reasonable.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"After we had had breakfast, we ________ the house.","a":"leave","b":"left","c":"had left","d":"has left","answer":"2","explain":"\n- After + past perfect tense, simple past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"I had heard the news before you ________ me about it.","a":"tell","b":"told","c":"has told","d":"had told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense+ before + simple past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"It ________ when I got up this morning.","a":"rains","b":"rained","c":"had rained","d":"was raining","answer":"4","explain":"\n- When + Simple past tense, simple past continuous.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary was not feeling well when she ________ down yesterday.","a":"fall","b":"fell","c":"has fallen","d":"had fallen","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When + Simple past tense, simple past continuous.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"He signed the contract after he ________ each statement carefully.","a":"reads","b":"read","c":"has read","d":"had read","answer":"4","explain":"\n-After + past perfect tense, simple past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}